<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Inauguration Day &#8211; Anugraha</title>
	<atom:link href="https://nihalybaig.github.io/AnugrahaWP/tag/inauguration-day/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://nihalybaig.github.io/AnugrahaWP</link>
	<description>Value Based Education</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 20:23:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://nihalybaig.github.io/AnugrahaWP/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/favicon.ico</url>
	<title>Inauguration Day &#8211; Anugraha</title>
	<link>https://nihalybaig.github.io/AnugrahaWP</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Anugraha Women’s College, Kalladka – Inaugurated on 29/6/2013</title>
		<link>https://nihalybaig.github.io/AnugrahaWP/2016/04/15/awc-inaugration/</link>
				<comments>https://nihalybaig.github.io/AnugrahaWP/2016/04/15/awc-inaugration/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nabil89]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Annual Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inauguration Day]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://oceanwp.org/travel/interdum-magna-augue-eget-copy/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Minister for Forest, Environment and Ecology and Dakshina Kannada District-in-charge B Ramanath Rai on Saturday formally inaugurated &#8216;Anugraha Women’s Degree College’ at Kalladka in Bantwal taluk.Speaking on the occasion, Minister for Health and Family Affairs U T Khader appreciated efforts of management and staff and wished all round success of the college.In the introductory address, [&#8230;]]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Minister for Forest, Environment and Ecology and Dakshina Kannada District-in-charge B Ramanath Rai on Saturday formally inaugurated &#8216;Anugraha Women’s Degree College’ at Kalladka in Bantwal taluk.Speaking on the occasion, Minister for Health and Family Affairs U T Khader appreciated efforts of management and staff and wished all round success of the college.In the introductory address, Amanulla Khan, Vice-Chairman of Anugraha Educational Trust, presented the objectives of Anugraha Institutions emphasizing value based comprehensive education system.</p>
<p>The institution offers a blend of education and ensures combination of faith and reason, intellect and wisdom. It is an endeavor to infuse the spirit of human values in the veins of the future mothers of the society. The college aims at providing an atmosphere for the achievement of the self-knowledge and discipline inculcating the virtue of good citizenship strengthening their faith in God and love towards humanity, concern towards the poor and the weak. To achieve above objectives, the college has selected such a staff that is well versed both in academic education and in character building. As such, the students on completion of the degree course will have developed integrity in character deeply loyal to God with unbiased love towards humanity and obtained basic knowledge of family health care and home science. Also they shall realize purpose of life, understand family values, be dutiful to parents, respect to teachers, value fellow humans, realize duties and obligations, also due rights, differentiate what is right and wrong, truth and falsehood etc, he said.</p>
<p>Sharfuddin B S, Kuwait, presided over the program. Chandraprakash Shetty, Member of Zilla Panchayath, Dakshina Kannada, Aida Suresh,Member of Taluk Panchayath, Bantwal, Moulana Yahya Thangal Madani, Khatheeb-Havva Juma Masjid, Bolangady, Shameera Jahan, Asst. Organizer, Ladies Wing, JIH Karnataka, Mohammad Haneef Haji, Hajjaj Groups, Golthamajal, and Mahfooz ur Rahman were also present. Audience consists of Students, Parents and local citizens of Bantwal taluk.</p>
<p>The Government of Karnataka has granted permission on June 12, 2013 under affiliation to Mangalore University. Accordingly, degree college classes for the year 2013-14 commenced from June 17 this year..</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://nihalybaig.github.io/AnugrahaWP/2016/04/15/awc-inaugration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
